safetype.com 2019-02-25

# Privacy Notice - SafeType

Thank you for visiting this website. We hope you enjoy learning more about ErgoType BV and our products.

ErgoType respects your right to privacy in the on-line world when you use this website or communicate electronically with us. We have therefore developed this Privacy Notice to inform you how ErgoType BV (“ErgoType”, “we,” or “our”) collects, stores, uses and processes the personal information you provide us through this website. 

By using this website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice. If you do not agree to this Privacy Notice, please do not use this website. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Notice at any time. Any changes will be posted in this Privacy Notice and material changes will generally apply only to activities and information collected on a going forward basis. We encourage you to regularly review this Privacy Notice to make sure you are aware of any changes and how your information may be used.

Here at ErgoType we take your privacy seriously and will only use your personal information to administer your account and to provide the products you have requested from us.

We will never use your personal information to contact you for anything else than providing you with information regarding your order.

We will never pass your details onto other companies.

We only use cookies that are necessary to support your visit on our website and the ordering process.

Please be informed that ErgoType BV is the Data Controller of any personal information you submit to ErgoType.

If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to this Privacy Notice please contact us.
